I'll be outside.
I'll take off your shirt
to see what you got.
All right?
I looked up to your father.
He and my big brother
were like two heroes to me.
Your grandfather
should end up as they did.
When my nephew told me
what you were doing...
I was afraid for you.
But now...
the war has started.
We have to finish it.
I'm nearly done.
Give me your arm.
Change the bandage twice a day.
And rest.
Take these after every meal
or it'll get infected.
Thank you.
There's a lot of people
counting on you.
I hope you know what you're doing.
I do.
I'm going to see Italo.
Hello?
Baby. where are you?
Listen. things went wrong. You gotta run.
Take Mico and find my grandfather.
Do what he says.
Your grandfather?
Stefano. what happened?
How did it go?
Good.
How did he say he got shot?
He didn't tell me. why?
Because they didn't shoot him.
He shot himself.
Peace.
My name's Omar. I'm a friend
of Mohamed Hamaha.
Mohamed was killed
by the French yesterday.
Who are they?
Americans.
I'm sorry about Mohamed.
I don't like Americans.
- Bring them a blanket.
- Okay.
For the cold.
Peace be with you.
- How's it going?
- Well and you?
Well.
Let's go.
Peace.
Get out.
Easy.
Tell her to go back in the car!
- Stay in the car!
- Easy.
Easy. easy.
You stay in the car.
Stay in the car! Stay there!
Where's my brother?
Do you speak French?
Breaking news: there's been another
terrorist attack in Ouagadougo.
where a handful of extremists
are holding dozens of people hostage
in a hotel in the heart of the city.
Gunfire was heard close to the hotel
but there is no information
regarding casualties.
Authorities have not received any
demands for the release of the hostages.
One of the attackers
has been identified as Tamil Yiarango.
son of militant Brahim Yiarango.
We have not yet established
whether Yiarango senior
is one of the attackers.
Over to Bernard Erting
at the scene of the attack.
The attack was carried out
by four armed men
who opened fire
on a crowded French restaurant.
The patrons
were brought into the hotel...
There's been an attack!
French Special Forces.
They're all dead.
Everyone is dead.
Go.
Careful. Check.
No men on the left.
Go. go!
Wait.
Go check.
About six men.
Okay. go.
Press hard.
Press hard. Like this.
Wear this tonight.
I wore it in when I married your mother.
You are my favourite son.
Say goodbye to mother for me.
He's an American doctor
with World Peace Doctors.
He has to examine some patients.
- Good evening.
- Your access permit.
Are you Dr. Christopher Lynwood?
- And these men are with you?
- Yes.
You've come.
Who is he?
Let me see my new baby.
Where's Tamil?
He's on his way to God.
God is great.
There is no other God but Allah.
Water.
Here.
Let's go!
- What's he doing here?
- He was with them.
Hurry! Quick!
Don't let Brahim die!
Get him inside.
You. beat it!
Beat it! Go on. beat it!